Sean Carlson

Wiew my Portfolio Site!▶ 952.288.5758➤ carlsonseanr@gmail.com

in Connect with me on LinkedIn!

A lifelong learner, and energized by complex problems, I discovered my passion for software development after graduating with my Bachelor's in Communication. I have over 1 year of Full Stack Developer experience and I am eager to continue growing my skill set. I pride myself on continuously increasing the value I provide to my community, and I am looking to deliver my potential to an organization that shares my motivation.

RECENT EXPERIENCE

CyberMinds Consulting | Full Stack Developer

2022 - Present | Remote

- Contribute to Requirement Analysis and Product Development
- Collaborate with the Development Team on a React.js/Django Application
- Meet the business requirements of a web application with software development solutions

Carlsean.com | Full Stack Developer

2021 - 2022 | Remote

- View my portfolio site with the link in the top right of this page, or visit https://carlsean.com/
- This Site was built to showcase my skills as a developer, and to display three of my personal projects
- The section at the bottom of this resume shows the technical skills I've developed in my experience

Parker Personal Care Homes | 1:1 Direct Support Professional

2019 - 2022 | Arvada, CO

- 2021 Colorado Direct Support Professional of the Year Semi-Finalist
- Provided support to people with developmental disabilities in a day program/community setting
- · Carefully observed interfering behaviors to determine root causes and design informed solutions
- Reported independent observations to a team and workshopped successful intervention techniques

EDUCATION

University of Minnesota Duluth | Duluth, MN

Bachelor of Arts

Communication Major, Economics Minor

Coding Bootcamp | Remote

freecodecamp.org

- Responsive Web Design Certification (~300hrs)
- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures Certification (~300hrs)
- Front End Development Libraries Certification (~300hrs)

SKILLS

- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- React.js
- jQuery
- Bootstrap

- Express.js
- Node.js
- API's
- AJAX/JSON
- Ruby
- Django

- MongoDB
- SQL
- PHP
- REST
- Git
- GitHub